<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<project>
	<task id="0@1" status="Active" tags="">
		<title>
			Getting started with GTG
		</title>
		<donedate>
			2009-02-19
		</donedate>
		<subtask>
			1@1
		</subtask>
		<subtask>
			2@1
		</subtask>
		<subtask>
			3@1
		</subtask>
		<subtask>
			4@1
		</subtask>
		<content>
			Welcome in Getting Things Gnome!, your new task manager. 

In GTG, everything is a task. From building a bridge over the Pacific Ocean to changing a light bulb or organizing a party. When you edit a task, it is automatically saved.

Once a task is done, you can push the &amp;quot;Mark as done&amp;quot; button. If the task is not relevant anymore, simply press &amp;quot;Dismiss&amp;quot;. 

A task might be composed of multiple subtasks that appear as links in the description. Simply click on the following link :

&lt;subtask&gt;1@1&lt;/subtask&gt;

Don't forget to mark this subtask as done !

Other stuffs you should read
&lt;subtask&gt;2@1&lt;/subtask&gt;
&lt;subtask&gt;3@1&lt;/subtask&gt;
&lt;subtask&gt;4@1&lt;/subtask&gt;

We hope that you will appreciate GTG. Please send us bug reports and ideas of improvement on :
https://bugs.launchpad.net/gtg

Thank you for trying out GTG :-)

		</content>
	</task>
	<task id="1@1" status="Active" tags="">
		<title>
			Learn to use subtasks
		</title>
		<donedate>
			2009-02-19
		</donedate>
		<content>
			In the task description (this window), if you begin a line with &amp;quot;-&amp;quot;, it will be considered as a &amp;quot;subtask&amp;quot;, something that needs to be done in order to accomplish your task. Just try to write &amp;quot;- test subtask&amp;quot; on the next line and press enter.

You can also use the &amp;quot;insert subtask&amp;quot; button.


Task and subtasks can be re-organized by drag-n-drop in the tasks list.

Some concept come with subtasks : for example, a subtask due date can never be after its parent due date.

Also, marking a parent as done will mark all the subtasks as done.

		</content>
	</task>
	<task id="2@1" status="Active" tags="">
		<title>
			Learn to use tags
		</title>
		<content>
			A tag is a simple word that begin with &amp;quot;@&amp;quot;.

Try to type a word beginning with @ here :


It becomes yellow, it's a tag.

Tag are useful to sort your tasks. In the view menu, you can enable a sidebar which display all the tags you are using so you can easily see tasks for a given tag. There's no limit to the number of tag a task can have.

If you right click on a tag in the sidebar, you can also set its color. It will permit you to have a more colorful list of task, if you want it that way.

		</content>
	</task>
	<task id="3@1" status="Active" tags="">
		<title>
			Using the workview
		</title>
		<content>
			If you press the &amp;quot;workview&amp;quot; button, only actionnable task will be displayed.

What is an actionnable task ? It's a task you can do directly right now.

It's a task that is already &amp;quot;startable&amp;quot;, so the start date is already over. 

It's a task that don't have opened subtasks. So it means you can do the task directly.

Thus, the workview will only show you tasks you should do right now.

If you use tags, you can right click on a tag in the sidebar and choose to not display tasks with this particular tag in the workview. It's very useful if you have a tag like &amp;quot;someday&amp;quot; that you use for task you would like to do but are no particularly urgent.

		</content>
	</task>
	<task id="4@1" status="Active" tags="">
		<title>
			Reporting bugs
		</title>
		<content>
			GTG is still very alpha software. We like it and use it everyday but you will encounter some bug.

Please, report them ! We need you to make this software better. Any contribution, any idea is welcome.

If you have some trouble with GTG, we might be able to help you or to solve your problem really quickly.
		</content>
	</task>
</project>
